* 1. [Politics](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/politics "Politics")
            
            1. [Reviews](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/reviews "Reviews")
            2. [So surprising](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/so-surprising "So surprising")
            3. [Sport](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/sport "Sport")
            4. [World News](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/world-news "World News")
            
        2. [Funny](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/funny "Funny")
            
            1. [General News](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/general-news "General News")
            2. [Interviews](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/interviews "Interviews")
            3. [Music](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/music "Music")
            
        3. [Columns](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/columns "Columns")
            
            1. [Community News](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/community-news "Community News")
            2. [Culture](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/culture "Culture")
            3. [Did You Know?](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/did-you-know "Did You Know?")
            4. [Entertainment](https://www.the-latest.com/topics/entertainment "Entertainment")
            
* Search form
    -----------
    
    Search 

PRIVACY STATEMENT
=================

You don't want your personal information to fall into the wrong hands. Neither does THE-LATEST.COM.

THE-LATEST.COM is committed to protecting your privacy. We keep your data secure and we do not use it for any other purposes. We will never share your data with third parties.This policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you.

**What information do we collect about you**

You can visit our website without disclosing any personal information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may request information from you. We collect information you give to us by email, various forms on the website, over the telephone, face to face or by postal mail. We collect information about you when you make a donation, become a supporter, place an order for our products, complete an online action, sign a petition, provide us with data about your campaigning interests or interact with our social media tools. Website usage information may be collected using cookies.

**How will we use the information about you?**

We will send you information by email or SMS that we think may be of interest to you. We will continue to send you information by post where we have assessed there is a legitimate interest for us to do so. Please contact us if you would like any of your information removed.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

**Access to your information and amending your information**

If you would like a copy of some or all of the personal information we hold about you, please email [contribsed@the-latest.com](mailto:contribsed@the-latest.com) - We may make a reasonable charge for this service (eg, for repeated requests). We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate. We will retain some basic information to avoid sending you unwanted materials in the future and to ensure we do not duplicate information.  This is superseded by your right to erasure (“the right to be forgotten”).  Following this request all of your data will be removed from all THE-LATEST.COM systems and any financial agreements, such a Direct Debit, will be ended.

**Cookies**

Cookies are text files, used by your computer’s browser, that store visitor session data. Cookies, by themselves, do not identify the individual user. Cookies are commonly used on the Internet and do not harm your system. If you want to know more about cookies please go to [www.allaboutcookies.org which](http://www.allaboutcookies.org which) explains how cookies work and how you can manage their use.  
We currently use cookies to collate general management data which is used to plan enhancements to our services. Some cookies are external managed e.g. GoogleAnalytics and are covered by their own privacy policies.

THE-LATEST.COM never stores any personal information in cookies (on any computer that you may use) that can be used to identify you, such as your name, email address or account numbers.  
If you do not want us to use cookies you may be able to configure your browser not to accept them. Please refer to your browser’s ‘help’ facility for further information. However, in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.

**Other websites**

Our website – THE-LATEST.COM contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to our website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.

**Transfer of your data internationally**

The DPA and GDPR restrict the transfer of data outside of the EU and EEA. Our primary web server is located in the UK, however some of the suppliers and systems that we use can be based in other countries which are outside of the EU and EEA. This may occur, for example, by using online services with servers based in other countries or which route data via such  will ensure that information which you provide is only transferred to other countries (which do not have data protection laws equal to the DPA and GDPR) provided that the organisations involved have certified under the EU-US Privacy Shield (for organisations based in the USA) or similar stringent certification to ensure that adequate safeguards are in place to protect your rights and your data.

**Changes to our privacy policy**

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and will place any updates on this webpage. This privacy policy was reviewed and updated in May 2018.  

**Who to Contact**

If you have previously submitted personal data through the site and would like that information deleted from our records and database, please contact us at our email address:

We will make every reasonable effort to delete this information from our existing files and confirm with you the deletion of your personal data.

Your privacy is important to THE-LATEST.COM, as is your trust in our services. We want you to know that the information we collect will be treated with the utmost care.

**Data Protection**

The-Latest Ltd appears on the public register of Data Controllers. Our registration details and purposes can be viewed at [https://ico.org.uk/ESDWebPages/Entry/ZB257594](https://ico.org.uk/ESDWebPages/Entry/ZB257594)

 © Copyright 2018 THE-LATEST.COM

#### LEGAL

These terms and conditions govern your dealing with The-Latest Ltd that owns and operates the website The-Latest.com. References to the The-Latest.com are to be taken as a reference to The-Latest Ltd unless the context otherwise indicates.

These terms and conditions state the terms on which you are permitted to use the site, what your obligations to The Latest are, and what our obligations and exemptions from liability to you are. As we are a not-for-profit social enterprise, we claim the fullest exemptions permitted by law.  

#### Information

#### Latest Tweets

* RT [@mowords](http://twitter.com/mowords): The Home Office says most grooming gangs are white but the Home Secretary is determined the focus should stay on Br… [https://t.co/aSMRp16mA2](https://t.co/aSMRp16mA2)
* Please register, spread the word, and attend [https://t.co/ulG8SqNTBz](https://t.co/ulG8SqNTBz) [https://t.co/HdgyFpBi4O](https://t.co/HdgyFpBi4O)
* RT [@mrjamesob](http://twitter.com/mrjamesob): Exactly 200 years after William Wilberforce founded the Anti-Slavery Society, here’s Suella Braverman at a facility… [https://t.co/gOBuJwFgdW](https://t.co/gOBuJwFgdW)
* RT [@SpacesSteve](http://twitter.com/SpacesSteve): [#ImWithGary](https://twitter.com//search?q=%23ImWithGary) This was the tweet people of twitter spread it far and wide. GARY LINEKER speaks for the people. [https://t.co/p0hPz3J3yL](https://t.co/p0hPz3J3yL)
* RT [@RefugeeTogether](http://twitter.com/RefugeeTogether): Banning people who cross by small boat from claiming asylum? It's wrong. Plain and simple. Here's why...

#### Journalism Tips

© Copyright, 2015 The-Latest.com

The-Latest.com is not intended for readers or contributors under 18 years of age. All copyrights and trademarks on this page are owned by The-Latest and their respective owners. Content on this site cannot be reproduced without the prior consent of the editor. If consent is given then the name of 'The-Latest.com' must be published as a credit.

Fixed & Maintained by [Kolabris Digital Solutions](https://kolabris.com/ "kolabris.com")
